Guide to the New-York Historical Society Museum Department Records 1765, 1830-2018 NYHS-RG 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Collection Management Files, 1929-2008; 36.93 Linear feet
  - Subseries IV.B. Outgoing Loans, 1939, 1947, 1976-2005; 1976-2002; 20.21 Linear feet
    - OLR-1983.6. Nassau County Museum of Fine Art, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.7. National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.8. The Hudson River Museum, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.9. The Hudson River Museum, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of frame damage.
    - OLR-1983.10. Jefferson County Historical Society, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.11. Museum and Library of Maryland History, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.12. The Heckscher Museum, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.13. The Edith C. Blum Art Institute, The Bard College Center, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.15. The Detroit Institute of Arts, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.16. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.17. The Connecticut Historical Society, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.18. Cragsmoor Free Library, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1983.19. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1983, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1984.1. The Historic New Orleans Collection, the Kemper and Leila Williams Foundation, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4)
    - OLR-1984.2. Philadelphia Museum of Art (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.3. Memorial Art Gallery, University of Rochester (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.4. Louisiana Department of Wildlife and Fisheries (2 folders) (Offsite-box 5)
      Includes a polaroid photographic print of the requested items as exhibited.
    - OLR-1984.5. California State University, Long Beach, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.6. The Columbus Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.7. The Edward Hopper Landmark Preservation Foundation (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.8. The Dog Museum of America, American Kennel Club Foundation, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.9. Daughters of the American Revolution Museum, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
      Includes a piece of label from the back of the frame of a painting from the N-YHS collections (The Schuyler Family by Ambrose Andrews) that was found in the wrappings of the painting upon receipt by the DAR Museum.
    - OLR-1984.10. Fraunces Tavern Museum (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.11. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.12. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.13. University of Virginia Art Museum (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.14. The Emily Lowe Gallery, Hofstra University, 1983 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.15. C. M. Russell Museum (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1984.16. Hudson River Maritime Center, 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 48)
    - Library: Art Commission of the City of New York, City Hall, 1984 (Offsite-box 5)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1984, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.2. Columbus Museum of Art, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.3. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.4. Albany Institute of History and Art (Executive Mansion), 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 5)
      Loan was made for the purpose of display of paintings at the Governor's Executive Mansion in Albany, New York. Includes a photographic print of the requested item(s). Includes a brochure titled The Executive Mansion in Albany: A Century of New York History by Isabelle K. Savell (1982).
    - OLR-1985.5. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.6. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.7. Plimoth Plantation (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.8. The Art Museum, Princeton University (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.9. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 5)
    - OLR-1985.10. The Jordan-Volpe Gallery (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1985.11. Heritage Plantation of Sandwich (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1985.12. The Brooklyn Museum, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1985.13. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1985.14. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1985.15. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 6)
    - Museum: National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian, 1985 (Offsite-box 6)
    - Library: The Grolier Club, 1985 (Offsite-box 6)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1985, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.1. The American Museum of Natural History, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.2. Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.3. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.4. General Foods Collection, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.5. Historical Society of Rockland County, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.6. The Hudson River Museum, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.7. Museum of American Folk Art, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.8. Museum of American Glass at Wheaton Village (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.9. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College (2 folders), 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 6)
    - OLR-1986.10. Museum of the City of New York, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.11. The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.12. Nationalmuseum, Stockholm, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.13. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.14. The Parrish Art Museum, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.15. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 7)
      Includes photographic prints of the requested item(s) showing a conservation issue.
    - OLR-1986.16. Staten Island Historical Society, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 7)
      Includes issue of the Staten Island Historian newsletter dedicated to the exhibition.
    - OLR-1986.17. University Art Gallery, State University of New York at Albany, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.18. Tennessee State Museum, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.19. Krannert Art Museum, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 7)
      Includes exhibition catalogue.
    - OLR-1986.20. Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.21. Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.22. The Hudson River Museum, 1985 (Offsite-box 7)
    - OLR-1986.23. Albany Institute of History and Art (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
      Includes exhibition brochure and what appear to be N-YHS exhibit label(s).
    - OLR-1986.23. Albany Institute of History and Art (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1986.24. Museum of the Borough of Brooklyn, Brooklyn College, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1986.25. The Magazine ANTIQUES (Offsite-box 8)
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Library: The Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Library: Hopper House Art Center, 1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Library: Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1986 (2 folders), 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 8)
      Includes color slides of a requested watercolor Perspective View Near Newport, Rhode Island (x.483).
    - OLR-1987.3. The Anacostia Neighborhood Museum, Smithsonian, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1987.4. Bowdoin College Museum of Art, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1987.6. Delaware Art Museum, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1987.7. Huntington Galleries, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1987.8. International Exhibitions Foundation (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 8)
    - OLR-1987.8. International Exhibitions Foundation (2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.9. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.10. Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.11. The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.12. National Museum of Science and Technology (Canada), 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.13. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 9)
    - OLR-1987.14. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 10)
    - OLR-1987.15. The New York Public Library (Offsite-box 10)
    - OLR-1987.16. Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 10)
    - OLR-1987.17. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (2 folders), 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 10)
    - OLR-1987.18. Gettysburg National Military Park, National Park Service (6 folders), 1986-2000 (Offsite-box 10)
      This set of folders contains documentation regarding the long-term loan, additional items loaned, conservation treatment, a theft of a cutlass (object 1925.103), an extension of the loan, and return of the loaned items. Includes photographic prints (some of which are polaroid) and color treatment slides of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1987.19. The Navy Museum, Department of the Navy, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 48)
      Includes Kodak instant film photographic prints of certain requested item(s)
    - Museum: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987 (Offsite-box 10)
      Concerns a loan of Frederick Remington's Bronco Buster sculpture for the purpose of comparison.
    - Museum: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 10)
    - Museum: Mottahedeh, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 10)
      Concerns a reproduction arrangement with Mottahedeh with respect to reproduction of a piece of Staffordshire plate.
    - Library: Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Amon Carter Museum, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Erasmus Hall High School and Academy of the Arts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Utah Museum of Fine Arts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: International Center of Photography, 1986 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Fort Stanwix National Monument, National Park Service, 1987 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Library: Nippon Club, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
      includes a memorandum regarding a joint exhibition with the Nippon Club.
    - Library: South Street Seaport Museum, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1987 (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 11)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of certain requested item(s) and also photographic prints of a requesting institution's exhibition space.
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1987 (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 48)
    - Summaries of Loan Activity, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 48)
    - OLR-1988.1. Amon Carter Museum, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 11)
    - OLR-1988.2. Edith C. Blum Art Institute, Bard College, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - OLR-1988.3. The General Theological Seminary, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 11)
    - OLR-1988.4. Heritage Plantation of Sandwich, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.5. The Katonah Gallery (2 folders), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.6. Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.7. National Academy of Design, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.8. National Gallery of Art, Smithsonian, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.9. Kunsthistorisches Institut der Freien Universitat Berlin, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.10. Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 12)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints documenting conservation work performed by the requesting institution following damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1988.11. The Hudson River Museum, 1987 (Offsite-box 48)
    - OLR-1988.12. The University of Kentucky Art Museum, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 12)
    - OLR-1988.13. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - Museum: Luman Reed Exhibition, 1988 (Offsite-box 12)
      Contains receipts of delivery with respect to Asher B. Durand paintings.
    - Library: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - Library: Huntington Museum of Art, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 12)
    - Library: The Hudson River Museum (2 folders), 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 12)
    - Library: Grey Art Gallery, New York University, 1988 (Offsite-box 13)
    - Library: New York Public Library, 1988 (Offsite-box 13)
      Concerns delivery of certain insurance atlases to the New York Public Library for shipment with its similar material to a vendor for color microfilming.
    - Library: Amon Carter Museum, 1988 (Offsite-box 13)
      Found loose in files and put into a folder created by archivist.
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1988 (3 folders), 1975, 1987-1988, 1993 (Offsite-box 13)
    - OLR-1989.1. The Brick Presbyterian Church (Offsite-box 13)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1989.2. Musei Capitolini (2 folders) (Offsite-box 13)
      Includes some correspondence in Italian.
    - OLR-1989.3. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 13)
    - OLR-1989.4. Lehman College Library, CUNY (Offsite-box 13)
    - OLR-1989.5. Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 13)
    - OLR-1989.6. Museum of American Folk Art, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 13)
    - OLR-1989.7. Museum of the City of New York, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.8. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.9. Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.10. Princeton Historical Society (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.11. The Queens Museum, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.12. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Paris, France), 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.13. Washington State Capital Museum, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.15. National Gallery of Art, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 14)
    - OLR-1989.16. Historic Hudson Valley, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 15)
    - OLR-1989.17. The Connecticut Historical Society, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 15)
    - OLR-1989.18. Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 15)
      Includes exhibition brochure. See also folder OL-R1990.12. The Brooklyn Museum.
    - Library: South Street Seaport Museum, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: Whitney Museum of American Art at Phillip Morris, 1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: City of New York, Municipal Building, 1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: Meridian House International, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1988 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: U.S. Senate Commission on the Bicentennial, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: The Pierpont Morgan Library, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 15)
      Includes exhibition catalogues.
    - Library: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1988 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: National Archives, Mid-Atlantic Region, 1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Library: Historic Hudson Valley, 1989 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1989 (2 folders), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 16)
    - OLR-1990.2. Museum of the City of New York (2 folders), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 16)
    - OLR-1990.3. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (3 folders), 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 16)
    - OLR-1990.4. South Street Seaport Museum, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 16)
    - OLR-1990.5. Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 16)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1990.6. The Museum of Modern Art (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.7. The Octagon, The American Architectural Foundation (2 folders), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.8. Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
      Concerns loan of Flags on Fifty-Seventh Street, the Winter of 1918 by Childe Hassam for display in Mayor's office.
    - OLR-1990.9. Wadsworth Atheneum, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.10. The Museums at Hartwick College (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.11. The Heckscher Museum, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.12. The Brooklyn Museum (Offsite-box 17)
      See also folder OL-R1989.18. Corcoran Gallery of Art.
    - OLR-1990.13. The Brooklyn Museum, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.14. The Edith C. Blum Art Institute, The Bard College Center, 1985, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 17)
    - OLR-1990.15. The Berkshire Museum, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
    - Museum: Comune di Milano (City of Milan, Italy), 1990 (Offsite-box 17)
    - Museum: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1990 (Offsite-box 17)
    - Museum: The Jewish Museum, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 17)
    - Museum: Centre Georges Pompidou (2 folders), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: The Jewish Museum, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: The Alice and Hamilton Fish Library, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: Stadt Frankfurt am Mein Historisches Museum, 1990 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown at Federal Reserve Plaza, 1990 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: Staten Island Historical Society, 1990 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Library: The Library of Congress, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1990 (4 folders), 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 19)
    - OLR-1991.1. The Lockwood-Matthews Mansion Museum (Offsite-box 19)
    - OLR-1991.2. The National Museum of Sport (2 folders), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 19)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints and photographic print of damage to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1991.3. National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 19)
      Includes photographic prints of frame of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1991.4. Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 20)
    - OLR-1991.5. Katonah Museum of Art, 1991, 1996 (Offsite-box 20)
      Includes documents relating to two exhibitions.
    - OLR-1991.6. Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc., 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 20)
    - OLR-1991.7. The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 20)
      Includes exhibition checklist.
    - OLR-1991.8. Wadsworth Atheneum, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 20)
    - OLR-1991.9. The Brooklyn Museum, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 20)
    - OLR-1991.10. Allentown Art Museum, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Long-term loan: American Museum of Natural History, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Long-term loan: Phelps-James House, Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Long-term loan: National Park Service, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
      Concerns deaccession and donation of ten of thirteen prints to Federal Hall National Memorial, National Park Service, following a long-term loan to that institution.
    - Museum: Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Museum: National Academy of Design, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Museum: Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, University of Nebraska Lincoln, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
      Contains research-related request for photograph of Diana of the Tower sculpture by Augustus Saint-Gaudens and additional information such as provenance.
    - Library: Casa Italiana, at Low Memorial Library, Columbia University, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Library: Museum of the City of New York, 1991 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1991 (5 folders), 1988, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 21)
    - OLR-1992.1. Haggerty Museum of Art, Marquette University (2 folders), 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 21)
    - OLR-1992.2. McCord Museum of American History, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 21)
    - OLR-1992.3. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 21)
    - OLR-1992.4. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (3 folders), 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 22)
      Includes photographic negatives and prints of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.5. Museum of American Glass, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 22)
      Includes exhibition catalogue. Includes a key labeled "key for Museum of American Glass Box (ours)."
    - OLR-1992.6. Museo Mediceo (City of Florence, Italy) (2 folders), 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 22)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of packing related to the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.7. Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 22)
    - OLR-1992.8. National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 22)
    - OLR-1992.9. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian (2 folders), 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 22)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of the frame of requested item(s).
    - OLR-1992.10. War Memorial Museum of Virginia, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 22)
    - OLR-1992.11. Berliner Festspiele GmbH (2 folders), 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.12. Agnes Etherington Art Centre, Queen's University, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.13. The Octagon, The American Institute of Architects Foundation, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.14. The Taft Museum, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.15. Sordoni Art Gallery, Wilkes University (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.16. Gallery of Art, Washington University, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.17. National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.18. The Hudson River Museum (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.19. Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 23)
    - OLR-1992.20. L'Assessorato alla Cultura (City of Rome, Italy) (3 folders), 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 24)
    - OLR-1992.21. Florence Griswold Museum, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 24)
    - OLR-1992.22. Brandywine River Museum, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Museum: Queens Historical Society, 1992 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Museum: Gracie Mansion Conservancy, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Museum: Lake Placid Center for the Arts, 1992 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Library: National Archives and Records Administration, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 25)
    - Library: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 25)
    - Library: High Museum of Art, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 25)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1992 (3 folders), 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 25)
    - Summaries of Loan Activity, 1992 (Offsite-box 48)
    - Loan status reports, 1992, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 48)
      Contains lists of outgoing loans for the period of 1990 to 1992. Also includes information regarding the status of long-term loans as of 1991.
    - OLR-1993.1. Virginia Historical Society, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 25)
    - OLR-1993.3. The Baltimore Museum of Art (2 folders), 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 25)
    - OLR-1993.4. Williams College Museum of Art, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 25)
      Includes exhibition brochure and checklist.
    - OLR-1993.5. The Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1993-1995 (Offsite-box 26)
    - OLR-1993.6. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 26)
    - OLR-1993.7. The Hudson River Museum (2 folders), 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 26)
    - OLR-1993.8. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1993-1995 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Library: The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Library: Williams College, Archives and Special Collections, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Library: Bobst Library, New York University, 1993 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1993 (2 of 8 folders), 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1993 (6 of 8 folders), 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 27)